我在努力修复天堂
I'm trying to fix heaven.
Metatron也在努力修复天堂
Metatron is trying to fix heaven.
Metatron没有修复
Metatron isn't trying to fix anything.
他想毁了天堂
He's trying to break it.
天使
Angels.
在坠落
They're falling.
Matatron拿走了我的荣光
Metatron took my grace.
也就是说你是人类了
That means you're human.
Cass听我说
Cass,listen to me.
外面有很多天使
There're angels out there.
在找你 但是他们都暴跳如雷
They're looking for you and they're pissed.
就算只剩最后一口气 他们也会
Until their last breath,they will seek.
找出那个罪魁祸首复仇
Revenge on the angel that did this.
- 找出是谁毁了天堂 - 够了
- Who destroyed heaven - Stop.
还真不错 Clarence
That was beautiful,Clarence.
我们这次面对的是死神
We're dealing with a reaper.
化成灰我也能找到你
I can find you anywhere.
Sammy受伤了 伤得很严重
Sammy's hurt.He's hurt real bad.
这条祈祷面向所有天使
This one goes out to any angel.
我是Dean Winchester
This is Dean Winchester.
我需要帮助
And I need your help.
- 先说名字 - Ezekiel
- Start with a name - Ezekiel.
还有一个办法救你弟弟
There's a chance I can fix your brother.
从他体内救
From inside.
附身吗
Possession.
这种情况下 这算上上签了
This is the best from a bad situation.
如何救
How would it work.
我养伤的同时 也在帮Sam恢复
I heal Sam while I heal myself.
他可以在任何时候排斥我
Sam can eject me,at any time.
如果Sam真的排斥我
And if Sam does eject me.
他会死
He will die.
从现在起 我们就守住这个秘密
Yeah we'll keep it a secret for now.
Cassity主教
Monsignor Cassity.
星期六会来跟我们共进晚餐
Will join us for dinner on Saturday.
当然还会有很多人
And mass,of course.
他可能是挺烦的
He...can be a pain,so.
我们要保证大家各司其职
Let's have everybody on their toes.
先生们
Gentlemen.
我们在找一个人
We're looking for a man.
你们应该认识
We believe you may know.
他的名字是Castiel
He's name is Castiel.
嘿 Clarence
Hey,Clarence.
你还要跟我们待多久
How much longer you're gonna be with us.
今晚下班后就走
I'll be moving on tonight after work.
也是时候了
It's time.
我能问你个问题吗
Can I ask you something.
可以啊
Sure.
你会厌倦上厕所吗
Do you ever tired of urinating.
我怕是习惯不了了
I'll never get used to it.
Sam
Sam.
你在吗
You here.
嘿
Hey.
早安
Morning.
你这么早就出去了吗
You've been outside already.
对啊
Yeah.
睡醒了 出去跑两圈 日出很漂亮
Woke up,went for run,beautiful sunrise.
反正 收拾好自己
Anyways,cleaned up.
去买了早饭
Went to get breakfast.
给你带了 熏肉煎蛋 多油的
Grab you...real bacon and eggs,extra grease.
- 我都不用多想 - 真好
- Not even in an argue - Perfect.
等等
Wait.
你出去跑步了吗
You went running.
怎么了
What.
为什么你看起来很担心
Why do you look so worried.
现在的情况是 Cass
Let's see there's Cass who.
我几天前叫他来
I told to haul ass here,that was days ago.
他还在外面晃悠
He's still out there.
- 然后你 - 我怎么了
- There's you - Me.
我感觉很好啊
I feel great.
我知道
I'm sure you do.
但是Sam 你经过了试炼
But Sam,you went to the trials.
对吧 那可不是闹着玩儿的
Okay?That put a big strain on you.
我就觉得 你要是能
I just think it's better if you took.
慢慢来会更好一点 不是说表现的像
It easy,you know,and didn't act like you were.
像被天使附身了一样
Possessed by an angel.
他确实 很好
He does...feel better.
我们当然在努力
A work in progress of course.
我在很缓慢地治疗他
But I'm slowly healing him.
很好
That's great.
- 但是 - 我有新消息
- But - I have news.
我听到了天使们的私语
I picked up a chatter among the angels.
不全是以困惑为主题
Not all are wondering around in confusion.
嗯 有些在追杀Cass
Yeah,some of them are after Cass.
有一个小组
There's a faction.
很快被组织起来
That is rapidly organizing.
在找人类皮囊附身
And finding human vessels to contain them.
是Naomi的手下吗
Led by Naomi.
我从没听过那个名字 不是
I've never heard that name.No.
这个小组的高层
But it's this faction's leadership.
想找到Castiel
Who want Castiel found.
你也看到了Dean
You see,Dean.
我会很有用
I can be useful.
我弟弟也有用
So can my brother.
要不你去
So,why don't you go.
查查邮件什么的 我要是需要帮助
Checking email and if I need your help.
我会跟你说
I'll let you know.
- Dean - 我说了到时候我会跟你说
- Dean - I said I'll let you know.
我是说 你也知道 Cass
I mean,you know,Cass is.
现在是人了
Human now.
走这么远的路肯定要很久
He's gonna take a lot longer to travel.
总有一天我会被折腾死
I'm gonna get whiplash.
什么
What.
没事
Nothing.
好吧 我在想 如果
All right.I was thinking if.
如果天使们真的组织起来
If the angels are organizing.
情况就比我们想的要危险得多
That makes a lot more dangerous than we thought.
为什么你觉得他们有组织
Why do you think they're organizing.
这样才说得通啊
It makes sense.
我的意思是
My point is...that.
追Cass的天使越多 情况就越糟
The more of them that after Cass,the worse it is.
所以
So.
我们得找到他
We got to find him.
朋友们 就像我说的
Folks,like I've been telling you.
我们正处于一个最神圣的时刻
We're in the most sacred of times.
一位天使中的领导来到人间
A leader of angel reaches out for us.
你感受到他们的存在了吗
Can you feel their divine presence.
如果你能 请不要惊慌
And if you do,there's nothing to fear.
如果天使来敲门
You know,if angels were coming knocking.
请献出肉身
You just let them all in.
也让自己感受些许荣光
And fill yourself up with their grace.
我是牧师Buddy Boyle 这里是辉煌时刻节目
This is Rev. Buddy Boyle and Gold of Glory Hour.
祝大家所有人 最顺利度过一天
Wishing you a most blessing day.
阿门
Amen.
录完
And...we're clear.
很不错
Beautiful buddy.
能算是你最佳作品中的一个
One of your best.
这真是最好的赞赏了
That is highest praise sir.
还能亲眼看看上帝的特使
Seeing how your emissary for the man upstairs himself.
谢谢你 Bart
Thank you,Bart.
我叫Bartholomew
It's Bartholomew.
不得不说 上帝私下悄悄告诉我
And I have to say,God has personally assured me.
他对你工作的一切很满意
That he's highly pleased with your work.
他还准备了一份奖励
He prepare this special reward for.
要在人间 重新建立一个天堂
Helping a populated a true heaven on earth.
这么跟你说 对我来说
Between you and me,it's pratically.
作为为数不多 能听取一个
Reward enough for one of the few.
天使命令的人来说
Humans all the time,to get orders from a.
已经是荣幸之极了
Actual angel.
但是 如果真的准备了话
But...if he prepared.
我很荣幸
I'm honored.
太好了
Terrific.
先生 我准备好了
Sir,I'm ready.
我愿为基督献身
Let me be a vessel for devine.
我把自己的肉体交给您
I give myself over to you.
哈利路亚
Hallelujah.
是的
Yes.
嗯
Well.
如果你确定
If you're certain.
Bart
Bart.
怎么回事
What the hell.
兄弟
Buddy.
说简单点儿就是 不是所有
Simple truth is,not all who.
肉体都能装下天使的荣光
Are willing are designed to contain heaven's grace.
我们从今往后要考虑伤亡了
We have to expect a casualty now and then.
想想看 不过是一点儿小代价
It's a small price to pay when you think about it.
就像是替罪羊
Like the lamb of the sacrifice.
是的
Sure.
好吧 这是Cass星期二打电话的地方
All right So this is where Cass called from on Tuesday.
科罗拉多州的朗蒙特市
Longmont Colorado.
这些圆圈代表了不同时间 他可能到达的地方
Each circle is how far he might have gotten.
第一天 第二天 第三天
One,two or three days out.
好吧
Okay.
这儿
Here we go.
在他从朗特蒙市打来电话的同一天
Same day he called from Longmont.
那儿发生了一起奇怪的谋杀案
Weird murder,same town.
警察说一个小女孩儿
Cop said it was like the girl was.
自己爆炸了
Blasted from inside out.
天使杀人
Angel kill.
他们可能错过了Cass
They might have just missed Cass.
除非他们已经抓到了他
Unless they got him.
你是不是查到过一个埃默里公园 在爱荷华州
You got an Emory Park,Iowa.
埃默里公园 我刚才还看见来着
Emory Park...I just saw that.
离朗蒙特市有一段距离
Yep,a couple days outside the Longmont.
很好 因为
Okay,because.
周二的时候 两个牧师被杀了
Two priests were murdered there Tuesday.
眼珠迸裂 有被虐痕迹
Eyes blown out,evidence of torture.
被钉在了柱子上
They were impaled on post.
- 酷刑吗 是的
- Torture? - Yeah.
看来天使想要消息
Angels're looking for info.
要是他们先咱们一步找到Cass
Man if they get to him before we do.
是的
Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
我饿坏了
I'm so hungry.
- 你愿意分给我吃真是太好了 - 不用谢
- Very kind of you to share - It's okay.
我发现很多时候
You know I'm finding that often.
越是一无所有的人 就越是慷慨
People with the least to give are the most generous.
不管怎么说
Anyway.
我得有个更好的规划
I've got to plan better.
今天我的食物很快就吃光了
I ran out of food very quickly today.
你是第一次遇到这种情况对吧
You're new at this,aren't you.
吃饭
Food.
睡觉 放屁
Sleep,or passing gas.
都那么陌生
All very strange.
而且我突然发现
And it's occurred to me.
有一天我也会死去
That one day I'm gonna die.
我最好能睡着
I'd better try falling asleep.
难以入睡确实挺痛苦的
It's quite a process,isn't it.
试试数羊
Try counting sheep.
谢谢
Thanks once again.
什么羊
What sheep.
你变成人了吗
You're human.
对
Yeah.
嗯我觉得我认识你说的这个人
Yeah,I think I know this guy you're talking about.
听着像Clarence
Sounds like Clarence.
Clarence吗
Clarence.
教堂在镇子里经营着一处救济所
The church it runs a shelter in town and.
工作的人就能留下
We work here.We earn our keep.
Clarence待了几晚
Clarence's been a couple of nights and.
就走掉了
And then had to move on.
他走的那天 尸体也被发现了对吗
And he left the day that the bodies were found.
对啊
Matter of fact.
那两尸体太恶心的
Oh man,those poor guys were a mess.
死前一定受了不少折磨
They must have suffered bad.
但至少现在跟天使一起
But at least now they're with angels.
最好还是不要跟着天使混
I sure as hell hope not.
Clarence有说过他要去哪儿吗
Clarence happen to mention where he was headed.
没有
No.
他只说 他要一直不停往前
He just said...he always has to keep going.
他绝对来过这儿
All right,well,he's definitely been here.
好消息是他现在变得聪明点儿了
Good news is he's getting cagey.
用了个假名字 Clarence
Using a fake name,Clarence.
Meg以前这么叫他的
That's what Meg used to call him.
当然 他肯定还是不知道
Of course,he doesn't get that's the name.
这名字来自一个有名的天使
Of a pretty famous angel.
什么
What.
电影 风云人物
It's a Wonderful Life.
你真的不知道吗
Dude,seriously.
你找到什么了
What do you come up with.
另一个天使杀人
Another angel kill.
在拉斐特城外
Outside a town called Lafayette.
从这儿向东 一天的路程
About a day's travelled east here.
在什么地方 印第安纳州吗
What is that,Indiana.
对 尸体是在收容所发现的
Yeah,body was found in homeless camp.
尸体从内部被烧掉
Inside barbecues,the whole nine.
- 他是流浪汉吗 - 不是
- Homeless guy? - No.
从代顿城来的药剂师
A pharmacist from Dayton.
Boyle神父的影响力还真是大的惊人
Reverend Boyle's influence is astonishing.
我永远不会理解这群人
I'll never understand these people.
我们的兄弟姐妹正在快速找容器
Our fallen brothers and sisters are finding vessel.
比我们想象得快很多
Faster than we'd even hoped.
他们最好赶紧
They better.
之后要帮我去找Castiel
And then they need to help us find Castiel.
就是从你手掌心里逃走的人
You know,the one you let slip through your fingers.
安插在代顿市的探子正在追踪他
Our Dayton operative is tracking him.
很好 因为很明显
Good,because frankly.
你自己也危在旦夕
You're hanging by a thread.
什么事
What.
我们的探子找到了Castiel
Our operative did manage to find Castiel.
但是
But.
Castiel却以某种方式杀了他
Castiel was somehow able to kill him.
什么
What.
他是个疯子 长官
He's a mad man,sir.
- 非常危险 - 不
- And very dangerous - No.
我才是危险的那个
I'm very dangerous.
现在 立刻把那个疯子给我找到
Now you'll find this mad man.
把他彻底毁了
And you'll destroy him.
明白了吗
Do you understand.
这可能不大现实 长官
That may not be possible,sir.
我突然觉得你很烦人
I'm getting a little tired at you.
Castiel消失了
Castiel has vanished.
我们无法追踪到他
We're unable to track him.
他肯定找到了避开我们的办法
He must have found a way to ward himself against us.
求求你了 万能的主
Please Lord.
Mike是个好人
Mike is such a good man.
求你派天使来救救他
Please,send your angels to heal him.
感谢您的聆听
Thank you for hearing me.
阿门
Amen.
Mike是你的丈夫吗
Mike is your husband.
他病得很重
He's very sick.
是啊 人类
Yes,humans.
是如此的脆弱
So fragile.
直到最近我才真正体会到这份脆弱
I've never...never realized how fragile until recently.
所以我们祈祷
I guess that's why we prey.
有时境况是如此的不堪
You get in such a bad hand sometimes.
你需要找到比自己更强大的力量
You need something stronger than yourself.
多么美妙的想法啊 不过
What's a wonderful idea,but.
怎么
What.
万一你发现
What if you're to find out.
没有人在聆听你的祈祷
That no one is listening.
上帝已经离开
That God pretty much left.
天堂也不再体察人间疾苦
That Heaven had gone out of business.
你会怎么办
What would you do.
但那是不可能的
But that's not possible.
不 这是完全有可能的
No,I think it's completely possible.
你不明白
You're missing the point.
这是不可能的
It's not possible.
因为我对他们怀有信仰
Because they have my faith.
但如果我告诉你的是真相呢
But when I tell you the truth.
那是你的真相
Your truth.
不是我的
Not mine.
你缺乏信仰
You're lack of faith.
但这不等于我的信仰是无效的
It doesn't cancel what I believed.
不是这样的
That's not how it works.
知道吗
You know.
如果你像我一样 或许会好过一点儿
I think you might feel better if you tried it my way.
有人在聆听我的祈祷
Someone is listening.
现在的问题是
The issue is.
不知怎的 他现在可以避开我们的追踪
He somehow managed to ward himself against us.
我们追查到他的能力被干扰了
Our ability to track him has been jammed.
所以我们找到了你
Which brings us to you.
我的族人
In my kind.
总是能找到我们想要的人
We always get what we're looking for,Chief.
没错
Yes.
死神
Reapers.
但有些死神接的活计
But some of you have taken your scale set.
可不止这些
To a whole new level.
这只是传言
That's the rumour.
而且他们很乐意
And are willing to freelance.
接受雇佣
For a price.
传言是这样说的
That's the rumour.
跟我说说情况
Jump start me.
我该怎么着手寻找这个
How do I start looking for this.
Castiel
Castiel.
我只有一个词
I got one word for you.
Winchester
Winchester.
我见过的最惨的情况
Damaged thing I never saw.
受害者身上有一处刺伤
Vic had a stab wound.
但是
But.
那并不是他的死因
It's not what killed him.
- 他好像是从身体内部 - 蒸发一样吗
- Like his insides were - Vaporized.
大家都这么说
It's been going around.
那么
So.
死者是俄亥俄州的以为药剂师
This guy was a pharmacist from Ohio.
对
Apparently.
平凡小市民一个 信仰虔诚
Total family man,religious.
有一天突然把车停下
One day just stop his SUV.
毫无征兆的死在了桥上
Takes off,dies on the bridge from God knows what.
这是他的遗物
It's his staff.
请尽管翻看吧
Help yourselves.
谢谢
Thanks.
有发现吗
Anything.
没什么奇怪的
Nothing weird.
没品位的音乐
Crappy music.
一堆在线视频
A lot of pod casts.
都来自一个博主
All the same one.
Boyle兄弟走向光辉时刻
Heaven Buddy Boyle Going for Glory Hour.
警察说死者是个有信仰的人
The cop said he was religious.
跟我一起
Join me in a.
铸就辉煌的未来
Heaping helping of glory,friends.
如果你亲身见证神迹
When you're in the presence of the divine.
你就会知道
You'll know it.
如果你全身心的投入
And if you let yourself.
你就能听见
You'll hear it.
记住
So remember.
当天使降临
When angels come and knock in.
献出你的肉身
Let them all in.
天使需要得到许可才能附身人类 对吧
Angel can't possess a human without permission,right.
没错
Yep.
所以 天使在利用他寻找皮囊喽
So,what.They're using this guy to find vessels.
毕竟有那么多铁杆听众
It's a willing audience.
信仰虔诚
They're all religious type.
像咱们这位药剂师
Like our pharmacist here.
Boyle告诉他们把身体献给天使
Buddy Boyle tells them to let the angels take them over.
然后天使就夺走了身体主控权
And then body snatches.
这个Boyle的收视范围有多广
How big rates this Boyle guy have.
差不多覆盖全球
Pretty much the entire planet.
我不是偷
I'm not stealing.
我也不是警察
And I'm not a cop.
这难道不令人羞耻吗
It's a shame,isn't it.
有那么多饥饿的人 却有如此多的浪费
So much is wasted,while there're so many hungry.
我从不曾了解
I never knew.
来一块果冻花生酱三明治吗
Peanut butter and jelly.
味道很不错
It's pretty good.
不 我不能要你的食物
No,I can't take your food.
不 是我在给你
No,you're not.I'm giving it to you.
我自己也有过困难时期
Look,I've had hard times myself.
谢谢
Thank you.
再说一遍
Look,for a billionth of time.
我们只是来打听消息的
We're just looking for information,okay.
我们不是警察
We're not cops.
难道我们看起来像吗
I mean,do we look like cops.
是啊
Yeah.
好吧 我们不是警察
Well,we're not cops.
我们只是来找一个朋友
We're...just need to find a friend.
他处于非常时期
Who's in a deep.
那个男人被杀的当晚
Look,he might have been here at the night.
他可能在这儿
That guy was killed.
你们有人知道点儿什么吗
Were any of you hear then.
大概吧
Maybe.
很好
Okay.
他是黑色的头发
He's got dark hair.
蓝眼睛
Blue eyes.
可能有点怪怪的
A little out of it.
他可能会自称Clarence
He maybe call himself Clarence.
Clarence 我记得
Clarence,yeah.
你们经常聊天吗
You two talk.
不是经常
Not much.
还有什么吗
And.
我觉得他像是在逃命
Think he's on the run.
你看见他和那个受害者在一起了
You see him with the vic...victim.
没有
Nah.
还有吗
Okay.
他通常都去聚集区另一边睡觉
He went off to sleep in another part of the resor.
在哪儿
Where.
他现在不在
He's not there now.
那他去哪儿了
Where'd he go.
我看见他从桥下跑过去
I saw him running from under the bridge.
朝大路上方向去了
To the highway.
你是想继续跟我们挤牙膏吗
You gonna pay us for all this teeth pullin.
他到底去哪儿了
Where was he headed.
他爬到一辆往北走的卡车上 大概是底特律
He flagged a truck heading north,Detroit,probably.
为什么是底特律
Why Detroit.
卡车上写着 机动车城肉类特供
Truck was marked Motor City Meats.
真漂亮
It's beautiful.
可不是吗
If you say so.
事先声明一下
Just so you know.
我通常不会带陌生男人回家
I don't usually bring home strange men.
我很奇怪吗
Am I strange.
不 我是说
No,I mean.
我不认识的男人
Men I don't know.
你一副下过地狱的样子
You look like you've been to hell and back.
嗯 去过几次
Yes,a few times.
顺便 我叫April
April,by the way.
April Kelly
April Kelly.
Castiel
Castiel.
没有姓吗
One name.
就像God的名字一样
Like God.
或者Cher
Or Cher.
我不想惹人厌 但是
Not to raise any red flags but.
你知道你的胳膊正在流血吗
Do you know your shirt's soaked in blood.
看看这些化学添加剂
Look at these chemicals.
你都不读标签的吗
Do you even read the labels.
不
No.
我只看见派
I read pie.
剩下的字都是浮云
The rest of it it's just blah blah blah.
等咱们到了底特律
Listen,when we hit Detroit.
就从流浪汉避难所开始找
We start with the homeless shelters.
好的
Right.
然后去搜查营地 难民救济处
Then we go to the encampments,soup kitchen.
再去查查
Check out places that he.
他可能去打零工的地方
Might have gone looking for work.
我再去看看流浪汉逮捕记录
Yeah,and I can check for vagrancy arrests.
没错
Yeah.
还有
And you know.
离奇死亡案件
Odd death.
你是谁
Who are you.
你为什么跟踪我们
Why are you trailing us.
你管这堆破布叫绷带
You call this rag a bandage.
没感染算你走运了
You're lucky this wasn't infected.
那个袭击你的人怎么样了
What happened to the guy who attacked you.
我
I.
刺伤了他
Stabbed him.
他就爆炸了
He exploded.
有意思
Funny.
你看起来不像是会用刀子的家伙
You don't look like a knife fight type.
更像是个无家可归的可怜人
Rather a homeless type actually.
是啊
Yes,well.
我信错了人
I trusted the wrong person.
投资投错地儿了吗
Bad investment advice.
不 是自负
No,vanity.
我本以为我更重要
I thought I was more important.
更有影响力
More effective.
我以为
Than I am,that I could.
我能处理好一切
Fix everything.
但现在我只能不停的逃
And all I can do is keep running.
现在帮你包扎起来
Now I'll patch up.
你的肌肉都紧绷在一起了
But,God,your delts are in knots.
你需要放松下来
And you got to relax.
一切对我来说都是新鲜的
It's all new to me.
饥饿
Hunger.
寒冷
Cold.
还有这种感觉
This feeling.
孤独
Being all alone.
今晚你不是一个人
You're not alone tonight.
那么 Maurice
So,Maurice.
你那群特种部队一般的朋友
Your bounty hunters are like delta force reapers.
他们为什么找你盯上Cass
Why would they sic you on Cass.
他避开了他们的搜寻能力
He warded himself.
Naomi派你来的吗
Naomi hired you.
你俩在山里待多了吧
You really are out of the loop.
Naomi死了
Naomi is dead.
已经安息了
Rest in peace.
那现在谁在管事儿
So then who's running things now.
回答他
Answer.
她的昔日官僚
Her protege.
Bartholomew崛起了
Bartholomew.He's an up-and-comer.
他觉得
So he figured.
我们能带你找到Cass
We'd lead you to Cass.
所以这个所谓的Bartholomew
This Bartholomew.
现在是老大喽
He organizes the angels.
我只知道这么多
That's all I know.
你可以杀了我
You can kill me.
这不会改变什么
It won't matter.
如果我不找到Castiel
If I don't find Castiel.
别人也会
There are others that will.
下手吧
But do what you want.
乐意效劳
Sure.
说点什么
Say something.
没有语言可以形容
There aren't words.
所以说 还挺好的
So,that was okay.
非常好
Very much so.
我刚才
What I did.
表现的
That was.
还好吗
Correct.
非常好
Very much so.
太好了
Good.
Castiel 我忍不住在想
Castiel,I can not help thinking.
你之前说的话
You know,all that stuff you said earlier.
那些自责与内疚
Blame and guilt.
就好像
It seems like.
往这么好的一个人身上加了太重的负担
You're taking on a heavy load for such a sweet guy.
我做过很多愚蠢的
Believe me,I've done a lot of.
不明智的事情
Foolish,unwise things.
我不再是天使了
I'm no angel.
你信任的人
Whoever you trusted.
他们不能帮帮忙 解决困难吗
Can't they help,undo this.
我们没有联系了
We are not in contact.
那你接下来要做什么
So what happens next for you.
更多的这个 我希望
More of this,I hope.
我洗了你的衣服
I washed your stuff.
一切都好吗
Find everything okay.
事实上 有件东西找不到了
As a matter of fact,something is missing.
它之前在我的夹克里
It was with my jacket.
很难解释清楚
It's hard to describe.
你是说这个吗
You mean this.
怎么了
What's up.
我们整晚都在做无用功
We been chasing our tails all night.
没找到Cass
No Cass.
还问 怎么了 我现在很不爽
What's up?I'm fried.
该进行B计划了
It's time for plan B.
我不大明白
I'm not following.
我在让你知道
I'm letting you know.
好啊
Okay.
让我知道什么
Letting me know what.
我在让 你 知道
I'm letting you know.
什么事儿 Dean
What is it Dean.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
真荣幸
That is flattering.
我们谈过这个的
We've been through this.
我不能公然现身
I cannot be making public appearances.
这我明白
No,I understand that.
我又没让你走红毯 Zeke
I'm not asking you to red carpet Zeke,okay.
我需要你帮忙找到Cass
I need your help to find Cass.
没法做到
Can not be done.
他有办法避开追踪
He's warded.
我知道
I know that.
也许你可以用你
Maybe you can use your intergalactic.
宇宙无敌多维镭射眼 找找其他线索
Hyperspace,X-ray eyeballs to find someone else.
现在可能有个拿钱办事儿的死神在跟着他
There might be a reaper for rent on his ass.
你能找到它们吗
Can you find them.
我可以试试
I can try.
这没什么意义
It's probably pointless.
从你的衬衫上洗掉血迹
Washing the blood out of your shirt,really.
大概是真正的April会干出来的事儿
It's kind of thing that really April would've done.
我想念成为她的感觉
I miss being her.
她太好了
Very sweet.
一点也不介意我进入她
Didn't mind me entering her one bit.
你为什么不直接攻击我
Why didn't you just attack me right away.
我收到的简报是你很危险 很强大
My briefing said you were dangerous and powerful.
而且你确实有武器在身 所以
And you did arrive arm.So.
我需要信息
I needed information.
所以我必须赢得你的信任
So I had to gain your trust.
而那需要交媾
And that required intercourse.
是啊 我可以
Well,I'm allowed.
在执行命令时留有个人发挥空间
Leeway for executive decisions.
而且我不得不说
And I can't say.
你很有魅力
I didn't find you attractive.
谁派你来的
Who heired you.
我猜Naomi死去之后
I assume with Naomi gone.
事情都乱套了
Things were in chaos.
新官走马上任了 Cass
New sheriff in town,Cass.
他招揽了许多天使
He hired a bunch of us.
我很幸运
I got lucky.
你问得够多了
Enough questions from you.
现在换我问你
I have several of my own.
我们来谈谈你的密友Metatron
Let's talk about you buddy Metatron.
好吧 咱们再试一次
All right,let's try this again.
总有一次你会说出真相的
One of these times will get it right.
我一点也不知道Metatron的咒语
I knew nothing about Metatron's spell.
我不知道
I didn't know.
他要把天使驱逐出天堂
He was gonna casting the angels out of heaven.
我也被驱逐了
I was cast out,too.
真可怜
Oh dear.
不停重复一样的话可不够好
Nothing but reruns on this channel.
他的报酬很丰厚 是吗
These pays are marvelous,aren't they.
而且他这次也伤害了人类
He really do a number on humans,too.
我昨天晚上告诉你了
I told you last night.
我说的是实话 我当时很幼稚
And I meant it.I was naive.
我一点也不知道他打算做什么
I had no idea what he was planing.
你在说谎
You are lying.
大家都知道你帮Metatron进入天堂
It's known you helped Metatron enter heaven.
跟他勾结在一起
Collaborated with him.
因为我以为我们要修复天堂
Because we were going to restore heaven.
统一不同派系的斗争
Bring the factions together.
他对我说谎了
He lied to me.
他施咒的时候你和他在一起
You were with him when he unleashed the spell.
你知道天使们是怎么被扔下来的
You know how the angels were cast down.
我不知道他在集齐咒语
I didn't know he was assembling a spell.
我只知道
I only know.
我是最后的原料
That I was the final ingredient.
你
You.
我的荣光
My grace.
这就是为什么我变成了人类
It's why I'm human.
他把我的荣光加在咒语上
He took my grace to the spell.
或者是你给他的
Or you gave it.
要杀我是不明智的
It maybe unwise to kill me.
如果我的荣光是咒语力量的关键
If my grace was the key to empowering the spell.
我也可能是解开咒语的关键
I may be the key to countering it.
你是在跟我讲条件吗 Castiel
Are you negotiating with me,Castiel.
Cass
Cass.
来这么多男的啊 这姑娘还真火
This girl's popular with all the boys.
Cass Cass
Cass,Cass.
Cass
Cass.
不
No.
Sam 他没气了
Sam,he's gone.
Dean
Dean.
嘿
Hey.
我在
Yeah.
Sam
And Sam.
Cass你还好吗
Cass,you okay.
再也不许那样了
Never do that again.
好
All right.
但是我很疑惑
But I'm confused.
我知道她捅了我
I know she stabbed me.
但是我
But I'm.
好像没死
I don't appear to be dead.
你被敲晕了
You got dinged.
然后
And.
你
You.
我跟她做了交易
I made a deal with her.
说她要是把你带回来 我就不捅她
Said she wouldn't get kabobed if she brought you back.
她带你回来了
She brought you back.
你撒谎了
You lied.
是的
I did.
我就是撒谎了
I do that.
你从没回答过我的问题
You know you never answered my question.
你是怎么知道Cass在哪儿的
How did you know where to find Cass.
我跟你说了
I told you.
我翻了Maurice的兜
I went through Maurice's pockets.
找到一个地址 就去查了
I found an address and took a shot.
我从没见过你翻Maurice的兜
I never saw you go through Maurice's pockets.
你在说什么
What're you talking about.
我没见过你抱着书死啃
I don't see half of the nerdy stuff that you do.
这并不说明你不读书
It doesn't mean that you don't do nerdy stuff.
我真的很喜欢这个地方
I am really enjoying this place.
食物充足
Plentiful food.
水压很稳定
Good water pressure.
这些
Things I.
都是我以前从未考虑过的
Never even considered before.
人类真的需要考虑很多 对吗
There really is a lot to being human,isn't there.
我们的世界不仅仅只有墨西哥卷和脱衣舞娘
It ain't all just burritos and strippers,my friend.
是
Yeah.
我懂你的意思
I understand what you're saying.
是吗
You do.
人类生活中 人性的重要性大于生存的重要性
Yes,there's more to humanity than survival.
你们 寻求目标
You...look for purpose.
途中又不能被恼怒或绝望打倒
And you must not be defeated by anger or despair.
或者享乐
Or hedonism,for that matter.
怎么又扯到享乐上了
Where does hedonism come into it.
我跟April相处的时间 很具教育意义
Well,my time with April was very educational.
对
Yeah.I mean.
我能想到 跟一个要杀你的人在一起
I would think that getting killed is something.
做爱
And having sex.
你跟April滚床单了吗
You had sex with April.
对 所以他说到享乐
Yeah,that would be where the hedonism comes in.
你别插嘴
Shhh.
那
So.
有防御措施什么的吗
Did you have protection.
我有我的天使之刃
I had my angel blade.
人家有天使之刃
He had the Angel blade.
无论怎样 我
In any event,I.
我确实看到了生活的艰难
I do now see how difficult life can be.
看到了你们过得如此精彩
And how well you two have led it.
我觉得你们会是 很出色的老师
And I think you'll be great teachers.
谢了 Cass
Thanks.Cass.
还有墨西哥卷吗
Are there any more burritos.
有
Yes.
我们的小卡啊
Our little Cass.
他的第一次献给了死神 还真是
He gave it up to a reaper.That is.
Castiel不能留
Castiel cannot stay here.
他会将所有天使都引过来
He will bring the angels down on all of us.
不不 他纹了纹身
No,no,he's got the Enochian tattoo.
把自己屏蔽了
He's warded.
他的屏蔽时效只持续到April
He was warded when April found him.
杀了他
And she killed him.
对 但是你又让他回来了
Yes,and you brought him back.
我很感谢你 但是这可是Cass
And I thank you for that,but this is Cass.
我对你一无所知的时候
Okay,who vouched for you.
他为你做担保
When I didn't know you from Jack.
基地很安全
The bunker is safe.
Bartholomew在培养一支军队
Bartholomew is massing a force.
我们无法抵御任何入侵
We cannot stand an incursion.
Castiel有危险
Castiel is in danger.
如果他在这儿 我也就有危险
And if he is here,I am in danger.
你有危险
You're in danger.
哪儿来的危险 天使吗
From who,the angels.
如果他留下
If he stays.
我很抱歉 我只能离开
I am afraid I will have no choice but to leave.
不行
Oh,no,you can't do that.
Sam还没好全 如果你走了
Sam's not well enough.If you leave his body.
我知道
I know.
抱歉
I am sorry.
食物很不错 我快吃上瘾了
Epic food.I can't get enough.
Cass我们能聊聊吗
Cass,can we talk.
当然
Of course.
Dean你知道我一直很喜欢跟你聊天
Dean,you know I always appreciate our talks.
在一起什么的
Our time together.
听着 伙计
Listen,buddy.
你不能留下
You can't stay